Palestine
Marist College
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Material, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Indexed Photographs, 2.1.1.2.1
            - Palestine, 2.1.1.2.1.2
                - Graveyard on Mount of Olives, 1918; 48
                - Graveyard, Jerusalem in background, 1918; 49
                - Woman drinking tea (Lowell Thomas note: Gray hair to look as aged as possible), 1918; 50
                - Group of camels, 1918; 51
                - Two Indian troops on horseback, 1918; 52
                - Panorama of Jerusalem, 1918; 53
                - Military tractor and other vehicles, 1918; 54
                - Many Arab men standing with rifles, 1918; 55
                - Soldier sitting on camel as other man holds reins, 1918; 56
                - Arab man, woman and children in field, 1918; 57
                - Three men looking out over fields, man in center pointing cane, Lowell Thomas [?] at right with back to camera, 1918; 58
                - Outdoor amphitheater, two men on horses in foreground, Lowell Thomas [?] standing with back to camera, 1918; 59